Foundation for Child Development records, Accession 2012:052 FA421
Rockefeller Archive Center
Foundation for Child Development records, Accession 2012:052
1969-2003
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Foundation for Child Development
FA421
16.53 Cubic Feet 37 document boxes and 1 half-box.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment.
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Foundation for Child Development records were donated to RAC in 1998.
All records described in this guide were received by RAC in 2012, and accessioned as 2012:052.
At the time of ingest, the records were initially received in 13 standard record storage cartons (15.6 cu. ft.).
Conditions Governing Access
Records are open for scholarly research, with select files restricted (as noted).
In accordance with standard RAC policies, personnel records are restricted from scholarly access.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Other Finding Aids
FA019 Foundation for Child Development records; FA405 Foundation for Child Development (Guild for Crippled Children of New York City) records
Arrangement
Records are arranged in two series: Series 1 Grants; Series 2 Board of Directors.
Foundation for Child Development
- Grants, 1; 16.4 Cubic Feet
  Arrangement
  Grant records are arranged alphabetically by the name of the grant recipient.
  - ABT Health Care Research Foundation: Conference, Discretionary, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - The Advertising Council, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agenda for Children: State-based Child Advocacy/FSA, 1989-1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Albert Einstein College of Medicine: Richardson, 1992-1997, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1969, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences: Working Group on Public Policy for Children, Discretionary, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Academy of Pediatrics, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Association for Marriage and Family Therapy, Research and Educational Foundation: Family Impact Seminar, Discretionary Roundtable, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Association for Marriage and Family Therapy, Research and Education Foundation: Seminar on Family Income Security, 1992-1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 369)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Records are restricted from scholarly access - Personnel.
  - American Bar Association, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - American Forum
    - 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 1997 July - Present (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 2000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - FSA Media - Discretionary, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 1990, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - American Psychological Association, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - American Public Welfare Association
    - 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Commission on Child Welfare Reform, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Grantmakers Income Security Task Force - Discretionary, 1993 1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Media Outreach - Public Education - Part I, 1993-19943 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Media Outreach - Public Education - Part II, 1994 March-June (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Media Outreach - Public Education - Part II, 1994 July-Dec. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Annie K. Belding Memorial Fund: Abbey Medical Company, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Annie K. Belding Memorial Fund: Kagle Home Health Services, Inc., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Annie K. Belding Memorial Fund: New Alternative for Children, 1984, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Annie K. Belding Memorial Fund: Rehabilitation Equipment, Inc., 1982-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Annie K. Belding Memorial Fund: Respiratory Science Industries, Ltd., 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Annie K. Belding Memorial Fund: Winterkorn Orthopedic Appliance Company, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Arts Midwest, 1996-1997, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - The Aspen Institute, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - The Aspen Institute: Part I, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Association of Child Advocates: General Support, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Association of the Bar of NYC Fund, Inc., 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Austin Children's Museum, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Austin Children's Museum, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 370)
    Records are restricted from scholarly access -- Personnel Material.
  - Avance: Family Support and Education Programs: Neighborhood Research Grants Program, 1992-1999 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Photographs and Special Formats, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 41A)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the orginal file to facilitate stabilization, migration, and long-term preservation. The material is stored in Box 38.
  - Bank Street College, 1991, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Bank Street College of Education Analysis NYC Budget: Ch. Agenda, 1988-1990, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Avance: Family Support and Education Program, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Bazelon Center for Mental Health Law, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Bazelon Center for Mental Health Law, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Best Practices, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - The Better Homes Foundation, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Bettye Caldwell: Belding Scholar, 1986-1991 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Bettye Caldwell: Belding Scholar, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 371)
    Closed Personnel Material
  - Bronx Educational Opportunity Center
    - Bronx Educational Opportunity Center - Child Care Center, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Bronx Educational Opportunity Center - Child Care Center, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Bronx Educational Opportunity Center - Child Care Center, Inc., 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Bronx Educational Opportunity Center - Service Project, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - The Brookings Institution, 1999-2000, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - The Bushwick Community Service Society: Community-based Coor., 1988, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Case Western Reserve University: Neighborhood Research Grants Program, Korbin, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Catholic Legal Immigration Network, Inc., 1998-2001 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Center for Assessment and Policy Development
    - 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Part I, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Part II, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Part III, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Center for Assessment and Policy Development, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 372)
  - Center for Family Life, 1997-1999, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Center for Family Life in Sunset Park: General Support, 1992-1994, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Center for Family Resources, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Center for Innovative Public Policy: Discretionary, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Center for Law and Social Policy
    - 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - 1992, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Center for Young Children: Teachers College/Columbia University, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (CBPP)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - General Support, 1991-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Improving Financial Support for Low Income Families, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Child Care Action Campaign
    - Part I, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Part II, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Family Support Watch, 1990-1995 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - 1992-1994 (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Survey - State Response to FSA, 1989-1991, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Child Care, Inc.
    - 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Family Day Care Conference -Discretionary, 1994-1995, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Role of Family Day Care Networks in NYC, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Child Development Support Corporation
    - 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 89)
    - Service Project, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Child Trends, Inc.
    - 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 91)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 92)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Pt. I, 1995-1997, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Part II, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Discretionary, 1978, 1982, 1984, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Child Welfare League of America, Inc.
    - 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - 1996 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - Discretionary, 1991, 1995, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Children Now
    - 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - Citizen Action Campaign, 1988, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 102)
  - The Children's Aid Society
    - 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Milton Senn - Book, 1988-1991, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Children's Defense Fund
    - 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - 1993 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - 1996-1998, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - General Support, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Children's Express
    - 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Discretionary, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Election '92, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Citizen's Committee for Children of NY, Inc.
    - 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Study: Family Living Shelters for Alternative Housing, 1989-1992, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - CUNY/Children's Environments Research Group, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Coalition for Asian-American Children and Families, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Colorado Children's Campaign, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Columbia University
    - 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 120)
    - Center for Young Children, 1998-2000 (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - Child and Family Policy (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - Discretionary, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - Garfinkel, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 124)
    - K&K, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 125)
    - School of Social Work, 1990, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 126)
    - School of Social Work Seminar Series, 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 127)
    - Columbia University - Teachers College, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Columbia University in the City of NY, Trustees of, Meyers, 1997-2000 (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Community Food Resource Center, Inc.
    - 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 130)
    - Discretionary, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 131)
  - Committee for Hispanic Children and Families, Inc.
    - 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 132)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 133)
  - Connecticut Committee on Children, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 134)
  - Cornell University
    - 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 135)
    - Cornell University College of Human Ecology, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    - Cornell University - Early Childhood Programs, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 137)
  - Council on Foundations
    - 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - Discretionary, 1990-1997 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - Membership, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 140)
  - Court Appointed Special Advocates, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 141)
  - Denison University: Increasing Compensation, Education and Retention in Child Workforce, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 142)
  - Donor's Forum of Chicago, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 143)
  - Early Childhood Initiative, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 144)
  - Economic Policy Institute, 1998-2001 (Box 16, Folder 145)
  - Educational Broadcasting Corporation
    - 1994-1996, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 146)
    - Documentary, 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 147)
  - Educational Testing Service: FSA Contract, 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 148)
  - Erikson Inst.
    - 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 149)
    - History of Neighborhood - based Initiatives, 1992-1993, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 150)
  - Evanston Hospital Corporation: Neighborhood Research Grants Program, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 151)
  - Family and Work Institute, 1995-1998 (Box 16, Folder 152)
  - Family Dynamics, Incorporation: Pt. I, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 153)
  - Family Dynamics, Incorporation: Pt. II, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 154)
  - Family Resource Coalition
    - 1994-1996 (Box 17, Folder 155)
    - Discretionary, 1994-1995, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 156)
  - Federation of Behavioral, Psychological and Cognitive Sciences, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 157)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, Inc., 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 158)
  - The Finance Project
    - The Finance Project - Part 1-3, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 159)
    - The Finance Project - Part 4-5, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 160)
    - The Finance Project - Part 1-2, 1995-1997 (Box 17, Folder 161)
    - The Finance Project, 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 162)
    - Grantmakers Income Security Task Force - Welfare Information Network, 1996-1997, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 163)
    - Welfare Information Network - Part 2-4 (Box 18, Folder 164)
    - 1998 (Box 18, Folder 165)
  - Food Research and Action Center: Discretionary, 1992, 1995, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 166)
  - FCD Centennial Grant Awards, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 167)
  - FCD Internal Project: Neighborhood Research Grants Program, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 168)
  - French: American Foundation: Part I, 1997-2001 (Box 18, Folder 169)
  - French: American Foundation: Part II, 1989, 1996-2000 (Box 19, Folder 170)
  - Fund for Aging Services, Incorporated: Grandparents Raising Grandchildren, Discretionary, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 171)
  - Fund for the City of NY: ACT, 1994-1997, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 172)
  - Fund for the City of NY: HRA, Begin, 1993-1998 (Box 19, Folder 173)
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis, Inc., 1994-1996 (Box 19, Folder 174)
  - George Washington University: National Health Policy Forum, 1990-1995 (Box 20, Folder 175)
  - Georgetown University, 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 176)
  - Global Futures Foundation, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 177)
  - Good Shepherd Services: Family Case Management in a School Setting, 1990-1995 (Box 20, Folder 178)
  - Graham: Windham
    - Service Project, 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 179)
    - Welcome Home Program, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 180)
  - Grantmakers Concerned with Immigrants and Refugees, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 181)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth and Families, 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 182)
  - Grantmakers for Education, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 183)
  - Grantmakers in Health
    - 1995-1998 (Box 20, Folder 184)
    - 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 185)
    - Discretionary, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 186)
  - Grantmakers of Western PA, 1998-2002 (Box 21, Folder 187)
  - Greater Upstate Law Project, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 188)
  - Harvard, 1997-1999, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 189)
  - Harvard University Divinity School, 1999-2002, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 190)
  - Head Start: Begin, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 191)
  - Human Development Center of Mississippi, 1992-1994 (Box 21, Folder 192)
  - Jacob A. Riis Neighborhood Settlement House, 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 193)
  - Jewish Board of Family/Children's Services, Inc., 1999-2001 (Box 22, Folder 194)
  - Judge Baker Children's Center, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 195)
  - The Juvenile Law Center of Philadelphia, Inc., 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 196)
  - Labor Project for Working Families, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 197)
  - Labor Relations and Research Center: University of Massachusetts, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 198)
  - La Guardia High School, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 199)
  - The Legal Aid Society, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 200)
  - Leviticus 25:23, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 201)
  - Little Sisters of Assumption FHS: Family Life Program, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 202)
  - LSA Family Health Service: Family Life Program, Discretionary, 1991, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 203)
  - Living Hope Family Day Care Network, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 204)
  - Manpower Research Demonstration Corporation
    - Part 1-2, 1976, 1994-1998 (Box 22, Folder 205)
    - Observational Research in Jobs and New Chance - Part I, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 206)
    - Part II, 1991-1994 (Box 23, Folder 207)
    - Part III, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 208)
  - Massachusetts Committee for Children and Youth: Neighborhood Research Grants Program, Shay, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 209)
  - Mathematical Policy Research Incorporated: IDP/TPD, Part 1, 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 210)
  - Mathematical Policy Research Incorporated: IDP, Part 2, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 211)
  - M.B. Fund, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 212)
  - Mediascope, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 213)
  - MEM Associates, Inc., 2000 (Box 24, Folder 214)
  - Mid-Bronx Senior Citizens Council Inc., 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 215)
  - The Mississippi Forum on Children and Families, Inc., 1992, 1994-1997 (Box 24, Folder 216)
  - Monroe County Legal Assistance Corporation, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 217)
  - Morehouse College: Morehouse Res. Institute, Discretionary, 1993-1995 (Box 24, Folder 218)
  - National Academy of Sciences
    - 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 219)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 220)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 221)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 222)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 223)
    - Roundtable on Effective Services for Children, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 224)
  - National Academy of Social Insurance, 1994-1997 (Box 25, Folder 225)
  - National Association of Child Advocates: Pt. III
    - Part I, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 226)
    - Part II, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 227)
    - Part III, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 228)
    - Strengthen Child Advocates Capacity, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 229)
  - National Association of Social Workers: NYC Chapter, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 230)
  - National Black Child Development Institute, Incorporated: Helping Local Volunteers Develop Plan to Improve Subsidized Child Care in Local Communities, 1991-1994 (Box 25, Folder 231)
  - National Center for Clinical Infant Programs: Zero to Three, 1993-1996 (Box 25, Folder 232)
  - National Center for Early Childhood Work Force, 1996-1999 (Box 25, Folder 233)
  - National Coalition of Community Foundations for Youth, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 234)
  - National Committee to Prevent Child Abuse, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 235)
  - The National Committee for Prevention of Child Abuse, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 236)
  - National Conference of State Legislators
    - 1991-1995 (Box 26, Folder 237)
    - 1999-2004 (Box 26, Folder 238)
  - National Council of Jewish Women
    - Head Start Mental Health Services Survey - Discretionary, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 239)
    - West VA Youth Coalition - Discretionary, 1989-1991 (Box 26, Folder 240)
    - West Virginia Youth Coalition - State - based, 1990-1993 (Box 26, Folder 241)
  - National Governors' Association, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 242)
  - National Governors' Association Center for Best Practice, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 243)
  - National Head Start Association, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 244)
  - National Health Council Incorporated: Discretionary, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 245)
  - National Institute of Child Health and Human Development, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 246)
  - National Partnership for Women and Families, 2002-2004 (Box 27, Folder 247)
  - National Partnership for Women and Families: Support Materials, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 248)
    - Photographs and Special Formats, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 248A)
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the oringal file to facilitate stabilization, migration, and long-term preservation. The material is stored in Box 38.
  - National Public Radio, Inc., 1997-2000, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 249)
  - NRC Committee on Behavioral and Social Science Education, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 250)
  - New School for Social Research, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 251)
  - Neighborhood Funders Group, 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 252)
  - NY Academy of Medicine
    - 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 253)
    - 1998-2003 (Box 27, Folder 254)
  - NYC Partnership Fund, Incorporated: Early Childhood Ed. Pub. Serv. Campaign, Discretionary, 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 255)
  - The New York Community Trust
    - ACT- Part I, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 256)
    - ACT-Part II, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 257)
    - ACT- Part III, 1992-1997 (Box 28, Folder 258)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 259)
    - Base - Discretionary, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - COF Host Committee - Discretionary, 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 261)
    - Summer Youth - Discretionary, 1992, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 262)
  - The New York Immigration Coalition, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 263)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG), 1994-2001 (Box 28, Folder 264)
  - NYS Association of Deans of Social Work Schools, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 265)
  - NY State Child Care Coordinating Council
    - 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 266)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 267)
  - New York University (Box 11)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 268)
    - FCD History, 1994-1998 (Box 29, Folder 269)
    - Grant to Anne Marcus for a History of FCD, 1994-1995, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 270)
  - NY Urban League: The Urban Issues Group, Inc., 1995-1997 (Box 29, Folder 271)
  - The Pennsylvania State University, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 272)
  - Permanent Judicial Commission on Justice for Children Fund, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 273)
  - Phipps Community Development Corporation
    - 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 274)
    - HIPPY Program, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 275)
    - Service Project, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 276)
  - Population Resource Center
    - 1991, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 277)
    - Congressional Briefings, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 278)
  - Princeton University, Trustees of
    - Discretionary - Conference, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 279)
    - Office of Population Research - Fragile Families and Child Wellbeing, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 280)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 281)
  - Radcliffe College, 1997-2000 (Box 30, Folder 282)
  - Research Foundation for Mental Hygiene, Inc., 1997 (Box 30, Folder 283)
  - Research Foundation of the City University of NY
    - 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 284)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 30, Folder 285)
  - The Research Foundation of the State University of NY
    - Pilot Focus Group Project, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 286)
    - Support to JOBS Implementation Study, 1991, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 287)
    - Waters Study Disc., 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 288)
  - The Regents of the University of Minnesota: Institute of Child Development, 1997-1999 (Box 30, Folder 289)
  - Rockefeller University, 1998-2004 (Box 31, Folder 290)
  - St. Christopher: Ottilie
    - CFL, 1993-1996 (Box 31, Folder 291)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 31, Folder 292)
    - 1997 (Box 31, Folder 293)
  - St. Luke's: Roosevelt Hospital Center, Discretionary, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 294)
  - School of the 21st Century
    - 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 295)